KENNETH YU

Email: uyhtennek@outlook.com Phone number: 6315 6037

SUMMARY

I am a web and multimedia developer that has served museums and shopping malls. I have experience working in different teams, developing both back-end and front-end systems, and solving design problems. Knowing clients' and endusers' demands allowed me to provide memorable moments through my works. Having closed more than six projects with satisfied clients in a span of six months as a result.

WORK EXPERIENCE

WARE October 2024 - Current

Multimedia Developer

- · Collaborated with local museums to prep for coming exhibitions.
- · Delivered web projects with the LAMP stack, including 2 Web AR apps.
- · Suggested hardware and software solutions to use in projects.

Mass Modules

Multimedia Developer

- · Collaborated with schools, government organizations, and other corporate clients.
- · Developed multimedia apps using Unity, Kinect, Arduino and other technologies.

Minidragon September 2021 - October 2022

Junior Programmer

- · Ran a mobile game, which scored 4.8 stars in App Store.
- · Used Firebase and created tools to automate common requests.

EDUCATION

CLAP@JC X Generation

May 2024 - August 2024

Junior Full Stack Developer Program

- · Practiced using React.js, Vue.js, Express.js, MongoDB and PostgreSQL.
- · Completed 5 exercising related to CSS and JavaScript.
- · Explored UI design patterns and replicated them.

Technological and Higher Education Institute of Hong Kong

September 2017 - June 2021

B.S. in Multimedia Technology and Innovation (Cumulative GPA: 3.31)

- · Got a scholarship from Self-financing Post-secondary Scholarship Scheme Best Progress Award.
- · Participated in graphic design, video editing, and mobile app projects.

SKILLS

- · Time management; Communication skills; Analytical and problem solving.
- · MUI, shaden/ui, React, Vue, Figma, Canva, AI image generation
- · Vite, TypeScript, Express, Next.js, Redux, MongoDB, PostgreSQL
- · Git, GitHub, Cloudinary, GoDaddy, AWS, WordPress

March 2023 - August 2024